We were the most disjointed in the filming, weren't we?
We were.
You want to hear about that good morning?
Just now, right? Just now, with Kazuto and the others.
Where did you film?
I was at the park.
I was at the studio.
I was in the park.
It was a different park.
What?
I'm in the studio.
I've been in the studio all day.
So you haven't tasted the cold?
Out in this early in the morning?
Oh, my God, your knee.
Oh, God.
Cold wind, direct.
You have beautiful knees.
You're still in costume here.
There's one more place.
Another costume.
What's that?
Right here.
It's Luce.
Because she's a fox.
It's Luce in today's shoot.
Cute aggression.
I'm doing this, but Luce really likes me.
Kazuto's barking like crazy. Jun's barking like crazy.
She's drop-kicked.
Thinking? Think about it, Luce.
When it comes to foxes, two girls are the same
I like foxes.
What was that stroke?
How's it going? Does it calm you down?
How's it going?
Scootz.
Ceiling's so high!
We did the same ceiling as the top of Ryotan's dancestick.
Isn't it higher than you expected?
Oh, Jun wants it.
Already?
I'll take a look.
Okay.
Jun-kun's.
I'll show you.
I want to see.
I don't want to use this anymore.
I'm sorry...
I have to eat again today.
You know that, right?
You're eating at Teaching and Teaching.
You're the meal.
You're right.
Awww!
I had this by my side. I didn't think so.
Nice processing.
You're too much of an improv genius.
This time, I'm shooting a music video for a song called "Home Protection Anatai! We shot a music video for the song "Multiverse Adventure".
This time, we were shooting a music video for a song called "Multiverse Adventure," and we had two different outfits, one in plain clothes and the other in Asha's crisp outfit, for dancing and lip-syncing,
I feel that the music videos are becoming better and better with everyone's cooperation every time we shoot them.
When I shoot solo, it is fun to think about how the other members are doing it,
I think that this is one of the best parts of every music video shoot,
Please look forward to watching the music videos!
There will probably be more music videos to come, so I hope the other members enjoy them as well!
So, see you soon!
Thank you for watching!
Fast Forward
This time, the EP itself is quite conceptual. There are 6 songs, and each song is about 6 different worlds, and each story is about you, the person who exists in each world,
This multiverse adventure is a rather bright song, and the lyrics are quite philosophical,
The title song is a bright song that makes you feel spring, and I think it's very nice,
After that, there will be a lot more,
I think the music video will be a music video that embodies our unique style, which has always been in between 2-D and 3-D. I will do my best from here to the end.
I will do my best from here to the end.
I will work hard from here until the end.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for watching.
See you then.
See you.
Okay, we'll go first.
We're going to do a dance scene now.
I have to go back, so I'll do my best.
I'm going to make some choreography, and I'm going to make the middle of the choreography.
Yes, sir.
The distance should be a little wider.
But I don't know...
Like this.
A little bit bashful
No, it looks fine.
Okay, thank you.
Can I just check your swing for a second?
Sure.
I just want to make sure it's all there.
Half a body, half a body.
At this point, in front of your eyes.
Don't lean back, but keep this angle in line.
Yes, sir.
It's a half-body, but it's absolutely safe.
Just be careful at this point.
Don't get all excited.
Don't let the oven ring.
Let's have a cypher battle
All of it
Yes, ossan and
Let's go, old man.
Yes, yes, yes.
All right, all right, all right.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
If you make it that far, you're a winner.
Oh, come on.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's good.
There he is. There he is. There he is.
All right, that's it.
Start.
Oh, wow.
That's your type. That's your type.
Isollet bath type.
Isolé bath type.
Isollet bath type. - Isollet bath type.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I can't see your face.
I'm going to go get it.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
There's a genre for that.
Oh, rock.
Oh.
Ooh.
Oh!
As...
As.
Here you go.
Let's hear a little bit about the absolutely safe leg, too.
Absolutely secure, even though the legs are half-slit.
Absolute peace of mind
Absolutely secure
Even though I'm skeptical.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
What do you think?
It finally feels like we're shooting a music video.
I haven't danced from this morning to this evening.
I didn't dance from this morning to night.
I just did the image cut and danced with the boys at night.
I danced for the boys at night.
I finally feel like I'm in the middle of shooting a music video at night.
And one more thing...
There's another one with a different costume.
Well...
I know you are tired, but...
but we will all do our best
I'll do my best to make it an EMV.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I thought my body was sleeping.
Surprisingly, I'm fine.
I know.
I can tell.
I think the real battle is...
I think the real game is the scene after the costume change.
It's not over.
Oh! Oh!
Ooh!
Okay, you're with me.
Okay, bye.
I'm gonna go get dressed.
Bye-bye.
recommended
Thank you for watching.
I like your hair.
But I like Kazuto's haircut in the PRD MM the best.
I like Kazuto's haircut the best.
Museum Zero was
was the best!
Seriously.
That was awesome!
It was so cool!
Thank you for watching!